Guide to the Bingham Center Women's Zine Collection, 1992-2017 RL.01406
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2014-0159), 1992-2014; 1.5 Linear Feet; 2 boxes
  - Verandah Place (Box 41)
  - The Visible Woman (Box 41)
  - Voiceless Slut (Box 41)
  - Was That Supposed to Be Funny? (Box 41)
  - The Whirlwind (Box 41)
  - Womyn: The Queer Experience (Box 41)
  - Work Funnies (Box 41)
  - Xerography Debt (Box 41)
  - Yeah. So, I'm Fat (Box 41)
  - You've Got a Friend in Pennsylvania (Box 41)
  - Zine Librarian Pets (Box 41)
- Accession (2016-0141), 1992-2016; 2.5 Linear Feet; 5 boxes
  - 7 Minutes to Heaven (Box 42)
  - Acknowledgements Walt Whitman (Box 42)
  - All the Best Cowboys Have Daddy Issues (Box 42)
  - And the Devil Was Marching One by One (Box 42)
  - Angry Black-White Girl (Box 42)
  - Apocalipsa (Box 42)
  - ArtLife (Box 42)
  - BC Almanac (Box 42)
  - Birthday Party #1 (Box 42)
  - Black Sheets (Box 42)
  - Bound to Struggle (Box 42)
  - Brothers and Sisters, I Am an Atomic Bomb (Box 42)
  - CMYK (Box 42)
  - Chart Your Cycle (Box 42)
  - Cheer the Eff Up (Box 42)
  - Cherrybomb (Box 42)
  - Colored Girls Hustle Hard Mixtape (Box 42)
  - Cowgurl In My Head (Box 42)
  - Dear Women Who Are Experts: A Conversation to stave off craziness with love and wisdom (Box 42)
  - Empower Yr Sexy Self (Box 42)
  - Empty Orchestra (Box 42)
  - Every Thug Is a Lady: Adventures Without Gender (Box 42)
  - Feminist Zine Fest NYC (Box 42)
  - Finding a Place & Trusting It For Awhile (Box 42)
  - Fix My Head (Box 42)
  - Forget It (Box 43)
  - From Schtetls to Yarmulkes (Box 43)
  - Fuck and Paste (Box 43)
  - Gender Normality is Gender Morality (Box 43)
  - Gentrification at the Jackson St. Lot (Box 43)
  - Girls Rock NC (Box 43)
  - Go Fuck Yourself (Box 43)
  - High St. Este De Oakland Tierra De Lucha Y Limones (Box 43)
  - Ho Lover (Box 43)
  - Horoscopes For Astrologically Inclined Youths (Box 43)
  - How I Learned to Love Myself & Occasionally Other Men (Box 43)
  - How To Be a Riot Grrrl (Box 43)
  - I'd Start a Revolution (Box 43)
  - I Try (Box 43)
  - I Was a Teenage Satanist! (Box 43)
  - If I Could Turn Back Time (Box 43)
  - It's Complicated (Box 43)
  - Jetty (Box 43)
  - Kachorritxs Punks (Box 43)
  - Let Us Be Transparent (Box 43)
  - Let's Talk About DIY Sexuality Zines (Box 43)
  - Let's Wreck Their Precious Perfect Little Town (Box 43)
  - Lil Dope Fiend Overdose Prevention Guide (Box 43)
  - Malcriada (Box 43)
  - Mad Mulatta (Box 43)
  - Me Go On Without You (Box 43)
  - Moon Root (Box 43)
  - Muchacha (Box 43)
  - Musings Of a Jook-Sing (Box 43)
  - MXD Zine! (Box 43)
  - Neckmonster (Box 44)
  - Negativa (Box 44)
  - Negative Buttheads (Box 44)
  - Not Straight Not White Not Male (Box 44)
  - OCD and the GED (Box 44)
  - Olly Olly Oxen Free (Box 44)
  - On the Road to Healing (Box 44)
  - The Other (Box 44)
  - Paganstongue (Box 44)
  - Pasan Los Dias (Box 44)
  - The Philly Dudes Collective (Box 44)
  - Post-Punk Parenthood (Box 44)
  - Powder Box (Box 44)
  - Preta (Box 44)
  - Punk Door (Box 44)
  - Punkzine de Madres Padres Punxs (Box 44)
  - Queens, Hookers, and Hustlers (Box 44)
  - Ra(i)ze (Box 44)
  - Read Once & Destroy (Box 44)
  - The Real Ramona (Box 44)
  - REM Pt. 2 (Box 44)
  - Selected Texts from Late 2015 to Early 2016 (Box 44)
  - Serio? Social Justice Zine (Box 44)
  - Shameless (Box 44)
  - Slander (Box 45)
  - Sleep (Box 45)
  - South Knoxville Illuminated Gazetteer (Box 45)
  - The Spitboy Rule (Box 45)
  - Squatweiler (Box 45)
  - SRVIV (Box 45)
  - Stay Free! (Box 45)
  - The Swan and the Vulture (Box 45)
  - Team Kenan's 'Zine (Box 45)
  - That Girl (Box 45)
  - They Are Here With Us! (Box 45)
  - Think About the Bubbles (Box 45)
  - Three Dollar Bill (Box 45)
  - Tick Tock Biological Clock (Box 45)
  - Trash (Box 46)
  - Truth or Consequences (Box 46)
  - Truly the Shittiest Archaeologist Ever (Box 46)
  - Two Spirits (Box 46)
  - Unapologetic Choice (Box 46)
  - Urban Velocity Zine (Box 46)
  - Vital Signs (Box 46)
  - Wastelands (Box 46)
  - We Are Not White Lesbians (Box 46)
  - We Asked For Life (Box 46)
  - What's Their Name: More Adventures w/o Gender (Box 46)
  - Who Will Police the Police? (Box 46)
  - Woman's Ruin: Lust, Loss, and Other Lofty Ambitions (Box 46)
  - Women of Color (Box 46)
  - The World Is Big Enough Without You (Box 46)
  - Writing 101: Queer Spaces (Box 46)
  - Xicanistas Y Punkeristas (Box 46)
  - Zine Machine (Box 46)
  - Zinesboro (Box 46)
- Accession (2018-0048), 1992-2017; 1 boxes
  - Action-Packed, Action Research: How comic books, questions, and reflection can transform information literacy instruction (Box 47)
  - An activist approach to dealin' with Domestic Violence (Box 47)
  - AORTA Resource Zine (Box 47)
  - Archiving Your Group's Records: Your organizations live on @ the University Archives (Box 47)
  - Cat Power (Box 47)
  - Dr. Rad's Queer Health Show (Box 47)
  - Duke Department Of presents: V-Day Zine 2017 (Box 47)
  - Femicidio (Box 47)
  - The Feminist Make Space (Box 47)
  - Guide to Being a Straight Ally (Box 47)
  - Heteronormativity Blows: Queering the V-Day normative at Duke (Box 47)
  - Innerviews (Box 47)
  - Letters From Harriet (Box 47)
  - The Lookbook (Box 47)
  - Mixed Up! A zine about mixed race, queer + feminist experience (Box 47)
  - Nicey Hatey (Box 47)
  - Personal Archiving: Preserving our Digital Lives (Box 47)
  - Resist & Exist (Box 47)
  - Rubenstein Library Processing Manual (Box 47)
  - Sally Tatnall, Ohio Lesbian Feminist (Box 47)
  - Student Action with Farmworkers (Box 47)
  - True Colors (Box 47)
  - True Stories and Original Tales (Box 47)
  - Trump Reminds me of My Rape (Box 47)
  - We are all Nasty Women (Box 47)
  - Zine Librarians Trading Cards #f2fnyc17 edition (Box 47)